(Leonard:)Guys, our topic is
"Encouraging Women in Science."
Can you at least play a less sexist game?
(Sheldon:)How is it sexist?
(Sheldon:)My character wields a battle ax
as well as any man.
(Howard:)Not to mention she has mammary glands
that could nurse a family of 30.
(Howard:)And have enough milk left over
to open a Baskin-Robbins.
(Sheldon:)Mother, warrior-princess, franchise owner...
(Sheldon:)...I hear glass ceilings shattering
all over town.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you're always saying
how much smarter you are than me.
(Leonard:)Spend five seconds and come up with one
idea on how to get more women into science.
(Sheldon:)All your ideas address the issue
at a university level. By then it's too late.
You need to design a program that
targets girls at the middle-school level...
(Sheldon:)...and sets them on an academic track
towards the hard sciences.